I'M A MAN AGAIN
Mario Anibal Gimenez was born a man, but lived almost his entire life as a woman.
He even surgically implanted silicon breasts and pumped himself with female hormones
as his transsexual lifestyle took him across South America,
having relationships with different men.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua visited the nation of Paraguay in August 2017,
this is what happened when they met.
Man of God, help me. I want to be normal again.
Man of God, help me.
Man of God, help me, deliver me. I want to be like a man again. I want to be normal again.
I want to be normal again.
After the deliverance, his life transformed totally.
Anibal realised that the spiritual changes in his life after the deliverance needed to manifest physically.
After requesting for help from Prophet T.B. Joshua, the Emmanuel TV team paid for Anibal to undergo surgery
to remove the implants in his breasts, costing over 2000 USD.
It didn't end there.
The Emmanuel TV team took Anibal to a local mall to purchase male clothing,
items he had not worn for decades.
What followed next was an emotional reconciliation with members of his family and community,
all of whom were shocked at the dramatic turn around in his life after his encounter with Jesus Christ
at the Paraguay crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
If we fail to realise that there are powers that cause people to be bowed down in bondage,
we will continue to fight the wrong battle.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
Prophet T.B. Joshua says the evidence of Jesus Christ is lives changed.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
Right now, we are about to listen to the testimony of a young man whose life has completely transformed.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
Hello everyone! My name is Anibal. I am from Paraguay and am here today to share my testimony with you
and to show the evidence of what Jesus Christ has done in my life.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
I want to ask a question! Who believes in Jesus Christ?
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
I want to start from the beginning of my story, from when I was 12 years old until today.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
He said that he grew up thinking and believing that he was a girl.
It was even accepted in his family for him to behave like a girl.
He did his first surgery when he was 14 years old,
and he did an implant surgery when he was 14 years old.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
He said that because of this evil spirit that was inside of him,
he was behaving like a girl, and he was even taking female hormones to make his body
become like that of a woman's body.
After doing the surgery, at the age of 14, he felt much more like a woman physically,
and he began behaving more and more like a woman each day.
When he was 19 years old, he started taking female hormones.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
He never felt any affection for women; he rather had affection for men.
Before, in his past life, he was working as an artist, in the theatre, and was also into modelling.
Because he felt like a woman, he felt he could do more that any of the women that he was working with.
Although he had friendships with women, he never felt any affection towards them.
He only felt affection towards men.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
He spent so much money trying to become a woman, on surgery, operation, clothes, and everything.
He spent such a high amount of money.
And today, he feels that money was totally wasted because that amount of money
could have been used to help the needy, or do something else.
But he wasted all that money on trying to change, to become a woman, and it didn't work out.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
When he was 17 years old, he moved to Argentina which is a very liberal country.
In that country, he actually got married as a transsexual person.
During that time, he achieved everything he wanted humanly.
He had money, a reputation, a job, and everything. But yet, he was not happy, he was not satisfied.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
Six months ago, he received a terrible news that his mother had died.
When he went back to Paraguay, he was so depressed and he didn't want to go out of his home.
He felt there was nothing he could do, and life had no meaning for him.
Some neighbours came to try and advise him, counsel him, and he didn't want to listen to them.
Not until one day, they came and told him that he should go to a crusade in Paraguay.
He decided to go along with them to the crusade.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
He went to the crusade. From the moment he entered the crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
he felt as if he was with family.
He had lost his mother and his family, but God gave him a new family.
God gave him a wonderful family that now, his Father is Jesus Christ
and his second father is Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
At first, he didn't want to be prayed for by Prophet T.B. Joshua because of that spirit that was inside of him.
He kept resisting, and then finally, when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for him, he fell to the ground.
After he received that touch the second time, when he stood up,
until this very moment, his life has changed 100%.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
The first thing he noticed after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua during the crusade was that
he went to his house, and as he showered like normal every night,
he felt so uncomfortable with his long hair.
He felt so strange and he didn't like his hair again.
After that, he began to look at his body that had the female breasts and he didn't like that at all.
He felt so uncomfortable.
From that moment, he started looking at the female clothes
He wasn't comfortable and happy with himself.
So, he decided that he wanted to change.
But he realised he didn't have the financial means to do an operation to change physically,
although that change had happened inside of him.
So, he asked for help from the team of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
When he received a call from the team of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
that Prophet T.B. Joshua himself was going to pay for the operation to remove the breast implants
and buy a whole new wardrobe for him, of male clothing.
He was so happy that he didn't know what to do because this amounted to over 3000 USD.
Prophet T.B. Joshua also left one of his team in Paraguay to care for him, look after him,
be with him throughout the whole process, and buy a whole new wardrobe for him.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
From that moment, after the prayer with Prophet T.B. Joshua, he doesn't feel any affection for men anymore,
there's no attraction for men.
Rather, he feels attracted to women.
Now, as he's 30 years old, he would like to have his own child one day.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
He would like to advise everyone to learn from his own case.
Although he didn't even have to reach that side of prostitution, they should learn from him.
No matter the amount of money you spend on this earth -
he said he spent so much money, but that money could not make him a woman.
Today, he wants to tell everyone that he is what God created him to be, which is a man.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We believe there are many people watching you and many people here now who have a similar problem.
They are being disturbed by an evil spirit that is pushing them to engage in unnatural acts.
What is your advice to such people?
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
He said his advice is that you should not wait before you come for your deliverance.
Although it is never too late to change, remember that only God can deliver you.
This is a spiritual problem and only God can deliver you.
God is there! Jesus Christ can deliver you, He can set you free.
Watch Emmanuel TV, get connected, ask for help, go to a living church, and believe.
For faith, there is no barrier. For faith, there is no frontier because all things are possible for Jesus Christ.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
We thank God for your life and pray that God will give you the grace to maintain this deliverance
by making the Word of God the standard for your life.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
We want to remind everyone that as Christians, we are to love sinners but hate sin.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
So, our message is not to condemn those who are engaging in such acts,
but to fight the evil spirits responsible for them.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
We believe this testimony has encouraged millions around the world to also seek their own deliverance,
in the name of Jesus Christ and experience the freedom that this young man has received.
Mr Mario Anibal Gimenez Ruiz
Testimony From The Paraguay Crusade
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!